{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": "0",
      "deckName": "Kanji",
      "cardsLearning": "20",
      "cardsNew": "30",
      "cardsReview": "50",
      "cards": [
        { "front": "test1", "back": "answer1", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test2", "back": "answer2", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test3", "back": "answer3", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test4", "back": "answer4", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test5", "back": "answer5", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test6", "back": "answer6", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test7", "back": "answer7", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test8", "back": "answer8", "learningStage": "0" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "1",
      "deckName": "Hirigana",
      "cardsLearning": "20",
      "cardsNew": "30",
      "cardsReview": "50",
      "cards": [
        { "front": "test1", "back": "answer1", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test2", "back": "answer2", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test3", "back": "answer3", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test4", "back": "answer4", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test5", "back": "answer5", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test6", "back": "answer6", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test7", "back": "answer7", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test8", "back": "answer8", "learningStage": "0" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "deckName": "Katakana",
      "cardsLearning": "20",
      "cardsNew": "30",
      "cardsReview": "50",
      "cards": [
        { "front": "test1", "back": "answer1", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test2", "back": "answer2", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test3", "back": "answer3", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test4", "back": "answer4", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test5", "back": "answer5", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test6", "back": "answer6", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test7", "back": "answer7", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test8", "back": "answer8", "learningStage": "0" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "deckName": "Grammar",
      "cardsLearning": "99",
      "cardsNew": "30",
      "cardsReview": "50",
      "cards": [
        { "front": "test1", "back": "answer1", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test2", "back": "answer2", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test3", "back": "answer3", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test4", "back": "answer4", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test5", "back": "answer5", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test6", "back": "answer6", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test7", "back": "answer7", "learningStage": "0" },
        { "front": "test8", "back": "answer8", "learningStage": "0" }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
